--- GMAIL TOKEN DOCTOR ---
Checking Client ID: 6706933147... (Clean Length: 72)
Checking Secret: GOCSP... (Clean Length: 35)
Checking Refresh Token: 1//04... (Clean Length: 103)

Asking Google for an access token...
Γ£à SUCCESS! Google accepted your token.
Access Token starts with: ya29.a0AUM

--- CONCLUSION ---
Your credentials are VALID. The issue is likely hidden characters in the Railway variable UI.
